<?xml version='1.0' encoding='UTF-8'?>
<list>
    <quote>
        <content>Today, I am fortunate to have waken up. I am alive. I have a precious human life. I am not going to waste it. I am going to use all my energies to develop myself, to expand my heart out to others, to achieve enlightenment for the benefit of all beings.</content>
        <author>The Dalai Lama</author>
    </quote>
    <quote>
        <content>Perfection is achieved, not when there is nothing more to add, but when there is nothing left to take away.</content>
        <author>Antoine de Saint-Exupéry</author>
    </quote>
    <quote>
        <content>You cannot dream yourself into a character; you must hammer and forge yourself into one.</content>
        <author>Henry David Thoreau</author>
    </quote>
    <quote>
        <content>All of us, even when we think we have noted every tiny detail, resort to pieces which have already been stated enough by others.</content>
        <author>W.G. Sebald</author>
    </quote>
    <quote>
        <content>Language is like a cracked kettle on which we beat out tunes for the bears to dance to, while all the time we long to move the stars to pity.</content>
        <author>Gustave Flaubert</author>
    </quote>
    <quote>
        <content>Amid the seeming confusion of our mysterious world, individuals are so nicely adjusted to a system, and systems to one another, and to a whole, that, by stepping aside for a moment, a man exposes himself to a fearful risk of losing his place forever. Like Wakefield, he may become, as it were, the Outcast of the Universe.</content>
        <author>Nathaniel Hawthorn</author>
    </quote>
    <quote>
        <content>I prefer nothing, unless it is true.</content>
        <author>Socrates</author>
    </quote>
    <quote>
        <content>For my part I deem those blessed to whom, by favour of the gods, it has been granted either to do what is worth writing of, or to write what is worth reading.</content>
        <author>Pliny the Younger</author>
    </quote>
    <quote>
        <content>All great and honorable actions are accompanied with great difficulties, and must be both enterprised and overcome with answerable courante.</content>
        <author>William Bradford</author>
    </quote>
    <quote>
        <content>Be content with what you have; rejoice in the way things are. When you realize there is nothing lacking, the world belongs to you.</content>
        <author>Laozi</author>
    </quote>
    <quote>
        <content>And those who were seen dancing were thought to be insane by those who could not hear the music.</content>
        <author>Friedrich Nietzsche</author>
    </quote>
    <quote>
        <content>Things need not have happened to be true. Tales and dreams are the shadow-truths that will endure when mere facts are dust and ashes, and forgot.</content>
        <author>Neil Gaiman</author>
    </quote>
    <quote>
        <content>Fairy tales are more than true: not because they tell us that dragons exist, but because they tell us that dragons can be beaten.</content>
        <author>Neil Gaiman</author>
    </quote>
    <quote>
        <content>I want to stand as close to the edge as I can without going over. Out on the edge you see all kinds of things you can't from the center.</content>
        <author>Kurt Vonnegut</author>
    </quote>
    <quote>
        <content>No, you do not have thousands of years to live. Urgency is on you. While you live, while you can, become good.</content>
        <author>Marcus Aurelius</author>
    </quote>
</list>
